Contact

864-263-7733 (Work)

www.linkedin.com/in/bob-miller-cpc (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Sales Management Direct Sales Sales Trainings

Certifications

Certified Personnel Consultant (CPC)

Bob Miller

Providing Talent to Growing Companies

Greenville, South Carolina, United States

Summary

Do you view recruiting and interviewing as an unwanted chore? Even a necessary evil?

Have "Recruiting Firms" wasted your time? Or you've reviewed too many resumes? Or had new Hires quit?

We all want to hire very talented individuals. However, finding and evaluating top talent, and making sure the candidate is not only qualified for your opportunity, but also interested in your opportunity, takes time, resources, process and face-to-face interviews on our part.

This approach eliminates the guess-work of many of today's recruiting firms. It differentiates us and enables us to deliver a top talented hire to you within 2 or 3 candidates you interview through us.

Whether your hiring need is on a C-Level, VP, Director, Manager or Staff level, whether it is in Technology, Software, Supply Chain, or Sales, our approach, process, track record and experience can solve your hiring challenges.

https://www.bmarecruitingpartners.com/

Experience

Bobby M Affiliates
Executive Recruiter/President
August 2020 - Present (4 years 2 months)
Greenville, South Carolina, United States

Do you view recruiting and interviewing as an unwanted chore? Even a necessary evil?

Have "Recruiting Firms" wasted your time? Or you've reviewed too many resumes? Or had new Hires quit?

We all want to hire very talented individuals. However, finding and evaluating top talent, and making sure the candidate is not only qualified for your

opportunity, but also interested in your opportunity, takes time, resources, process and face-to-face interviews on our part.

This approach eliminates the guess-work of many of today's recruiting firms. It differentiates us and enables us to deliver a top talented hire to you within 2 or 3 candidates you interview through us.

Whether your hiring need is on a C-Level, VP, Director, Manager or Staff level, whether it is in Technology, Software, Supply Chain, or Sales, our approach, process, track record and experience can solve your hiring challenges. https://www.bmarecruitingpartners.com/

Wheaton McCrea

Owner

March 2013 - October 2023 (10 years 8 months)

Recruiting IT Professionals and Sales Reps, for firms from Start-up to Fortune 500 companies.

Clients include: TripAdvisor, Wyndham Hotel Group, Deutshce Bank, Goldman Sachs, JP Morgan Chase, Citi, AXA Financial, TIIA Cref, Aeropostale, Toys R Us, and many more.

Associated Personnel Services

Managing Partner

July 1979 - March 2013 (33 years 9 months)

30+ years of helping Clients' solve their recruiting issues and find good talent for their teams.

Education

Bucknell University

BS Math, Mathematics · (1975 - 1979)